Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Children: Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you!
我听不到你说话！
Children: Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
"And then,
the little ugly mollusk
ran all the way home."
“然后，
丑陋的小软体动物
一路跑回家。”
SpongeBob, you got to see this!
海绵宝宝，你一定要看看这个！
There's an emergency
broadcast on my TV.
有紧急情况
在我的电视上播放。
Man:  The day you've been
waiting for is almost here.
男：你去过的那一天
等待的时间已经快到了。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Glove World has a new ride.
手套世界有了新的游乐设施。
It's big.
它很大。
It's fast.
速度很快。
Harold, no!
哈罗德，不！
It's painful.
很痛苦。
It's the Fiery Fist O' Pain,
opening tomorrow,
only at Glove World.
这是炽热的痛苦之拳，
明天开业，
仅限手套世界。
Tomorrow!
明天！
SpongeBob, we got to get to bed
so we can be first in line.
海绵宝宝，我们得去睡觉了
这样我们就可以排在第一位。
Glove World.
手套世界。
Roller coaster.
过山车。
First in line.
第一个排队。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Which way to the Fist O' Pain?
哪条路可以到达痛苦之拳？
In the name of amusement, no!
以娱乐的名义，不！
I don't want to ride
the Fiery Fist of Pain!
我不想骑
痛苦之火之拳！
You ready to ride
the Fist of Pain?
你准备好骑行了
痛苦之拳？
No!
不！
Well, yeah.
嗯，是的。
It's just that I had
a bad dream last night.
只是我曾经有过
昨晚做了一个噩梦。
Really?
真的吗？
Me too.
我也是。
What was your dream
about, Patrick?
你的梦想是什么
关于，帕特里克？
Oh, look, the bus is here!
哦，快看，公共汽车来了！
SpongeBob: Wait for me, Patrick!
海绵宝宝：帕特里克，等等我！
Whoo, Fiery Fist of Pain,
here we come!
呼，痛苦的火拳，
我们来了！
Yeah, dudes.
是的，伙计们。
We're all riding
the Fist O' Pain.
我们都在骑行
痛苦之拳。
I heard somebody rode it
and his spine fell out.
听说有人骑过
他的脊椎骨脱落了。
Dude, I hope my spine falls out.
伙计，我希望我的脊椎骨脱落。
Yeah, me too.
是的，我也是。
Boy, the Fist O' Pain
sure sounds...
男孩，痛苦之拳
当然听起来……
...Really, really scary.
……真的、真的很可怕。
I mean, "fun-ifying."
我的意思是，“有趣”。
I mean, "hoi-tastic."
我的意思是，“hoi-tastic”。
I mean, "funable."
我的意思是，“有趣”。
Fun.
乐趣。
Really, really fun.
真的，真的很有趣。
Yeah, really fun.
是的，真的很有趣。
That sure looks like fun.
这看起来确实很有趣。
Yeah, I can't wait to ride it.
是的，我已经等不及要骑它了。
Tickets, please.
请买票。
No ticket.
没有门票。
I must've left it at home.
我一定是把它忘在家里了。
I swallowed my ticket.
我吞下了我的票。
I guess we're not going to be
riding the Fist of Pain today.
我想我们不会
今天骑着痛苦之拳。
Hold on a second.
等一下。
Here's your tickets,
in your back pockets.
这是你的门票，
在你的后口袋里。
Oh, barnacles.
哦，藤壶。
It sure was lucky
we found our tickets.
确实很幸运
我们找到了我们的票。
Yeah, bad luck.
是的，运气不好。
I mean, good luck.
我的意思是，祝你好运。
Very good luck.
祝你好运。
There it is.
就在那里。
That line looks awfully long.
这条线看起来非常长。
Oh, I know.
哦，我知道。
Let's go on some of
the dumb kiddie rides first.
让我们继续一些
傻孩子先骑。
Yeah, and then, the Fist of Pain
will seem even cooler.
是的，然后是痛苦之拳
会显得更酷。
Yeah.
是的。
Phew.
唷。
Can you believe some people are
afraid to ride roller coasters?
你能相信有些人是
害怕坐过山车？
Yeah, only a real baby would
be afraid of roller... Whoa!
是的，只有真正的婴儿才会
害怕滚轮...哇！
I can't believe it, Patrick.
我简直不敢相信，帕特里克。
It's Glovie Glove.
这是格洛维手套。
Get over there, and I'll take
your picture with him.
到那边去，我会带
你和他的合影。
SpongeBob: Get closer, Patrick.
海绵宝宝：靠近一点，帕特里克。
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
SpongeBob: Come on, closer.
海绵宝宝：来吧，靠近点。
That's it.
就是这样。
A little more.
再多一点。
Now hold on to his thumb.
现在抓住他的拇指。
Give me a big smile.
给我一个大大的微笑。
How do I look?
我看起来怎么样？
Wow, I look great.
哇，我看起来棒极了。
The Mitten!
手套！
I mean, the Mitten.
我是说，连指手套。
That ride's for babies.
那个骑行是给婴儿的。
Yeah, let's ride it just
to see how "babyfied" it is.
是的，我们就骑它吧
看看它有多“婴儿化”。
Hmph!
哼！
I guess that ride was too much
for the little guy.
我想那趟旅程太多了
为了这个小家伙。
Well, the line looks
a little bit shorter now.
嗯，这条线看起来
现在短了一点。
Can you believe some people
are scared of this ride?
有些人你能相信吗
害怕这次骑行吗？
Yeah, it's perfectly safe.
是的，这是绝对安全的。
No one gets hurt riding
these "roly" coasters.
骑行时无人受伤
这些“不倒翁”杯垫。
Why?
为什么？
Why, why?
为什么，为什么？
Why won't you
let me on the ride?
你为什么不
让我搭车吗？
Sir, you have
a serious medical condition.
先生，你有
严重的健康状况。
But it's my birthday.
但这是我的生日。
Oh, yeah!
哦，是啊！
One more time!
再一次！
You know, this is the line
for the bathroom.
你知道，这就是线
用于浴室。
We've gone eight times.
我们已经去了八次了。
And I went three times
all by myself.
而且我去了三次
全部由我自己。
I'm going to walk away now.
我现在要走开。
Bye.
再见。
Larry: SpongeBob, Patrick!
拉里：海绵宝宝，帕特里克！
Hello, Larry.
你好，拉里。
I just got off the Fist O' Pain.
我刚从痛苦之拳下来。
Man, what a rush.
伙计，真是太着急了。
Ah.
啊。
You smell that?
你闻到了吗？
That's the smell of adrenaline.
那是肾上腺素的味道。
Ooh, it's, um,
very manly, Larry.
哦，这是，嗯，
很有男子气概，拉里。
SpongeBob, I'm not smelling
any adrenaline on you.
海绵宝宝，我没闻到
你身上有任何肾上腺素。
You haven't gone on the ride?
你还没去搭车吗？
Um, I have a confession to make.
嗯，我有件事要坦白。
We haven't gone on the ride
because I'm hungry.
我们还没去搭车
因为我饿了。
I'm very hungry.
我很饿。
Hungry, hungry.
饿了，饿了。
Come on, Patrick.
来吧，帕特里克。
You and me, pal.
你和我，朋友。
I'm hungry too.
我也饿了。
Maybe I should stop
making people smell me.
也许我应该停下来
让人们闻到我的味道。
Want some?
想要一些吗？
No thanks, Patrick.
不，谢谢，帕特里克。
Um, you've got ice cream
in your eyebrows.
嗯，你有冰淇淋
在你的眉毛里。
Yeah, that's the problem
with this brand.
是的，这就是问题所在
与这个品牌。
I'll be right back.
我马上回来。
Hurry back, so we
can go on the ride.
快点回来，所以我们
可以去搭车。
"What's the matter, SpongeBob?"
“怎么了，海绵宝宝？”
Oh, delicious dairy treat,
I don't know what to do.
哦，美味的乳制品，
我不知道该怎么办。
"Patrick's your best friend.
“帕特里克是你最好的朋友。
You can't let him down."
你不能让他失望。”
I know, but the ride
is really scary.
我知道，但是骑行
真的很可怕。
"You want to see scary?
“你想看恐怖的吗？
I'll show you scary."
我会让你看到可怕的。”
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
噢，噢，噢，噢，噢。
"You like that?
“你喜欢这样吗？
You like that?
你喜欢这样吗？
Huh?
啊？
You like that?"
你喜欢这样吗？”
It's just a ride.
这只是一个旅程。
What are you so scared about?
你这么害怕做什么？
You can do it.
你可以做到的。
No, you can't.
不，你不能。
You're a big crybaby.
你真是个爱哭鬼。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是吗？
I thought we settled this
the last time.
我以为我们解决了这个问题
最后一次。
Ow, quit it.
哎哟，别说了。
SpongeBob, I have to
tell you something.
海绵宝宝，我必须
告诉你一些事情。
I have to tell
you something, too, Patrick.
我必须告诉
你也一样，帕特里克。
Man: Attention.
男：注意。
Glove World will be closing
in five minutes.
手套世界即将关闭
五分钟后。
Five minutes?
五分钟？
SpongeBob: What are
you looking at?
海绵宝宝：什么是
你在看吗？
Warning.
警告。
This ride may cause crying,
screaming, projectile vomiting
这次骑行可能会让人哭，
尖叫、喷射性呕吐
amnesia, spine loss,
embarrassing accidents,
uncontrollable gas...
健忘症、脊椎丧失、
尴尬的事故，
无法控制的气体...
...and explosive diarrhea.
...以及爆发性腹泻。
Is that all?
这就是全部吗？
Big deal.
有什么大不了的。
I did half that stuff
this morning.
我做了一半的事
今天早上。
Man: Last call for
the Fiery Fist of Pain.
男：最后的电话
痛苦之火拳。
Well, this is it, Pat.
嗯，就是这样，帕特。
Yup.
是的。
Here we go.
开始了。
ah-Ha.
啊哈。
On the Fiery Fist of Pain.
在痛苦的火拳上。
After you.
您先请。
We made it.
我们成功了。
Yeah.
是的。
Please keep your arms and legs
in the vehicle at all times.
请保留你的手臂和腿
始终在车内。
There.
那里。
Now if you could just
sign this release
现在如果你可以
签署此版本
absolving Glove World in case
of accidental spine loss...
赦免手套世界以防万一
脊椎意外丢失...
Well, nice knowing you.
嗯，很高兴认识你。
Ready in 10.
10点准备好。
Ooh, this is it, Patrick.
哦，就是这样，帕特里克。
Nine... Eight...
九……八……
We made it.
我们成功了。
Seven... Six...
七……六……
We're not scaredy-cats.
我们不是胆怯的猫。
Five... Four...
五……四……
We're not crybabies.
我们不是爱哭鬼。
Three... Two...
三……二……
We're brave.
我们很勇敢。
Man: Uh, we're experiencing
some technical difficulties.
男：呃，我们正在经历
一些技术困难。
Man, this cheap thing
is always breaking down.
老兄，这个便宜的东西
总是崩溃。
Hey, sorry, guys.
嘿，对不起，伙计们。
Maybe next time.
下一次吧。
Patrick, I have
a confession to make.
帕特里克，我有
坦白。
I was really scared
about going on this ride.
我真的很害怕
关于这次骑行。
Me too.
我也是。
I didn't know how
to tell you because, well,
I didn't want to disappoint you.
我不知道怎么办
告诉你因为，嗯，
我不想让你失望。
I didn't want you
to be disappointed in me.
我不想要你
对我感到失望。
But now we don't
have to face our fears.
但现在我们不
必须面对我们的恐惧。
The ride is broken.
骑行坏了。
Yeah!
是的！
Oh, wait.
哦，等等。
It's fine.
没关系。
Huh?
啊？
Have fun.
玩得开心。
SpongeBob: Patrick, I don't
want to face my fears.
海绵宝宝：帕特里克，我不
想要面对我的恐惧。
I'm afraid of 'em.
我害怕他们。
Good-bye, Patrick.
再见，帕特里克。
Good-bye, SpongeBob.
再见，海绵宝宝。
Woman: Please wait until the car
has come to a complete stop.
女：请等一下车
已经完全停止了。
And stop crying.
别哭了。
It's over.
结束了。
You can get out now.
你现在可以出去了。
We did it!
我们做到了！
We conquered our fears.
我们战胜了恐惧。
We stopped crying.
我们停止哭泣。
We survived the Fist O' Pain.
我们在痛苦之拳中幸存下来。
Hey, hold it right there.
嘿，就拿在这儿吧。
You forgot these.
你忘了这些。
SpongeBob and Patrick:
Our spines.
海绵宝宝和帕特里克：
我们的脊椎。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's go again.
我们再去吧。
Yeah.
是的。
Plankton: Oh, brother.
浮游生物：噢，兄弟。
Just look at this place.
看看这个地方。
Might as well be a mausoleum.
也可能是一座陵墓。
Abysmal.
糟糕透了。
Oh well, at least
it's structurally sound.
哦，好吧，至少
它结构合理。
Forget this.
忘记这个吧。
I'm sick of not
having any business.
我厌倦了不
有任何生意。
Karen: Then why don't you
fix this rust bucket up?
凯伦：那你为什么不呢？
修理这个生锈的桶吗？
Look around.
环顾四周。
Chipping paint, bad plumbing,
dust bunnies.
油漆剥落、管道不良、
灰尘兔子。
It's no wonder you don't
have any customers.
难怪你不
有任何客户。
OK, I get it, I get it.
好吧，我明白了，我明白了。
It's time to give this place
a complete overhaul.
是时候放弃这个地方了
彻底检修。
Whoa.
哇哦。
I shouldn't have to subject
myself to such menial labor.
我不应该屈服
我自己从事这种卑微的劳动。
This is a job for an imbecile.
这是一个低能者的工作。
Or two imbeciles.
或者两个低能儿。
Excuse me, gentlemen.
对不起，先生们。
I am sorry to bother you,
but I'm having a bit of trouble
with my abode.
很抱歉打扰你
但我遇到了一点麻烦
与我的住处。
You see,  , I would
like to paint the Chum Bucket
你看，我会
喜欢画密友桶
to please my wife, but alas,
I am too small and feeble.
为了取悦我的妻子，但可惜的是，
我太小太虚弱了。
Oh, well, we can help you.
哦，好吧，我们可以帮助你。
Right, Patrick?
对吧，帕特里克？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
I came prepared, too.
我也是有备而来。
All right, let's do it.
好吧，我们开始吧。
OK, boys, Karen wants this place
to really sparkle.
好吧，孩子们，凯伦想要这个地方
真正闪闪发光。
I was thinking it could use
a little more pizzazz.
我以为它可以用
多一点活力。
Pizzazz, yeah.
披萨，是的。
Hey, I know.
嘿，我知道。
Why don't you paint
the entire Chum Bucket?
你为什么不画画
整个密友桶？
Whoa, really?
哇，真的吗？
Oh, yes, I need
your artistic vision.
哦，是的，我需要
你的艺术视野。
You wouldn't want to disappoint
my Karen, now, would you?
你不想让你失望
我的凯伦，现在，你愿意吗？
No, uh-uh.
不，呃呃。
Well, hop to it, lads.
好吧，跳吧，小伙子们。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Woop-woop-woop-woop.
呜呜呜呜呜。
Heel, toe, heel, toe, heel, toe,
heel, toe, heel, toe.
脚跟，脚趾，脚跟，脚趾，脚跟，脚趾，
脚跟，脚趾，脚跟，脚趾。
SpongeBob and Patrick:
♪ Tra-la-la-la-la,
tra-la-la-la-la ♪
海绵宝宝和帕特里克：
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦♪
♪ We love to work ♪
♪ 我们热爱工作 ♪
What the...?
什么……？
SpongeBob, what atrocity
is this?
海绵宝宝，什么暴行
这是吗？
Oh, hi, Squidward.
哦，嗨，章鱼哥。
"Lookie."
“瞧瞧。”
Mr. Plankton's having us paint.
浮游生物先生让我们画画。
He calls it pizzazz.
他称之为“活力四射”。
Pizzazz, huh?
披萨，是吧？
What would you know about that?
你对此有何了解？
Plankton says he needs
our artistic vision.
浮游生物说他需要
我们的艺术视野。
Let's show him.
让我们给他看看。
You buffoons wouldn't know
artistic vision if it hit you
over the head.
你们这些小丑不会知道
艺术视觉如果它击中你
过头顶。
Now, where's a paintbrush?
现在，画笔在哪里？
I'll show you what
artistic vision is all about.
我会告诉你什么
艺术视觉就是一切。
Start with light brush strokes.
从轻的笔触开始。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah, perfect.
是的，完美。
Simpletons.
傻瓜们。
Amazing.
惊人的。
I didn't even have to trick
the tall one.
我什至不需要欺骗
个子高的。
My plan is falling
right into place.
我的计划落空了
就位。
With those three boobs
preoccupied, stealing
the formula will be a snap.
有了这三个胸
专心致志、偷窃
公式会很简单。
SpongeBob: Mr. Plankton?
海绵宝宝：浮游生物先生？
All this hard work
is making us thirsty.
所有这些辛苦的工作
让我们口渴。
Do you think
we could get a drink?
你认为
我们可以喝一杯吗？
Let me show you
something, SpongeBob.
让我告诉你
某事，海绵宝宝。
I sure wish I could offer you
a cold drink for all
your hard work
我确实希望我能为你提供
给所有人一杯冷饮
你的辛勤工作
but alas, my pipes
are rusted shut.
但唉，我的烟斗
都生锈了。
Ooh, I see what you mean.
哦，我明白你的意思了。
Yes, if only there was
some way I could...
是的，如果有的话
某种方式我可以...
Where'd he go?
他去哪儿了？
♪ La-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦♪
♪ La-la-la, la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦♪
Secret formula, here I come.
秘方我来了
SpongeBob: ♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la, la-la-la ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 啦啦啦啦，
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦♪
Perfect.
完美的。
Huh?
啊？
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
It's all wrong.
一切都是错误的。
Don't you know
a thing about art?
你不知道吗
关于艺术的事情？
Give me that brush.
把那把刷子给我。
Yes, yes, and yes.
是的，是的，是的。
Voila.
瞧。
A log cabin?
小木屋？
Yeah, I just think
they're so cozy.
是的，我只是觉得
他们很舒服。
Now, that's what you call art.
现在，这就是你所谓的艺术。
Everyone's a critic.
每个人都是批评家。
I can't wait to see
Krabs's face when he discovers
我等不及要看
蟹老板发现后的表情
that I've absconded with
the secret Krabby Patty formula.
我已经潜逃了
秘制蟹黄派配方。
SpongeBob: Hey, Plankton.
海绵宝宝：嘿，浮游生物。
What do you think
of the new window?
你觉得怎么样
新窗口的？
We got it from the Krusty Krab.
我们从 Krusty Krab 那里得到的。
SpongeBob, how do you
expect me to see out of
a window that high?
海绵宝宝，你怎么样
期待我看到
窗户那么高？
I guess I hadn't
thought about that.
我想我没有
想到了这一点。
Patrick: I did.
帕特里克：我做到了。
Look, Plankton.
看，浮游生物。
It's the perfect height
for your kind.
这是完美的高度
为了你的同类。
See, SpongeBob?
看到了吗，海绵宝宝？
Patrick's using the old noggin.
帕特里克正在用旧脑子。
He knows I'll actually want
to see out the window.
他知道我实际上想要
看看窗外。
Wait, you wanted
to see out the window?
等等，你想要的
看窗外？
Weird.
诡异的。
Uh...
呃...
Can't you two do anything right?
你们两个就不能做点什么吗？
I give you one simple task
after another, and...
我给你一项简单的任务
又一个，然后……
Just forget it.
忘记它吧。
It was foolish of me to think
this plan would ever work
我这样想真是愚蠢
这个计划会奏效
when nothing else in my life
has panned out.
当我的生活中没有其他事情的时候
已经成功了。
Telemarketing, lifeguarding,
creative writing,
all such bitter failures.
电话营销、救生、
创意写作，
所有这些痛苦的失败。
Oh, it's OK,
little, green... creature.
哦，没关系，
小的、绿色的……生物。
Patrick and I are gonna
keep working on the Chum Bucket
帕特里克和我要去
继续研究“密友桶”
until it's
the most "pizzazziest"
restaurant in bikini bottom.
直到它
最“热闹”的
比基尼下装的餐厅。
really?
真的吗？
And how.
以及如何。
Come on, fellows, let's do
some interior decorating.
来吧，小伙伴们，我们一起做吧
一些室内装饰。
Oh, good-bye, paintbrush.
哦，再见，画笔。
Hello, antique finish.
你好，仿古饰面。
Well, that ought to keep them
busy for a while.
好吧，这应该让他们
忙了一段时间。
Hup-hup-hup-hup,
hup-hup-hup-hup-hup.
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈，
哈-哈-哈-哈-哈。
Hup-hup.
嘻哈。
Hup-hup-hup-hup,
hup-hup-hup-hup-hup.
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈，
哈-哈-哈-哈-哈。
I just need to sneak past Krabs
and I'm home free.
我只需要偷偷溜过蟹蟹
我现在自由了。
Hup-hup-hup-hup-hup.
哈-哈-哈-哈-哈。
Where could that stingy crab be?
那只吝啬蟹会在哪里呢？
Hup-hup-hup-hup-hup-hup.
哈-哈-哈-哈-哈-哈。
Still don't see him.
还是不见他。
Hup-hup-hup-hup-hup.
哈-哈-哈-哈-哈。
The safe.
保险箱。
I'm in the clear, baby.
我很清楚，宝贝。
It's beautiful.
很美丽。
No, no tears.
不，没有眼泪。
Not yet.
还没有。
There's work to be done.
还有工作要做。
At long last.
终于。
And the secret formula is,
one bottle of molting lotion.
秘密公式是，
一瓶蜕皮乳液。
Take passport photo.
拍摄护照照片。
Get new safe, travel size.
购买新的旅行保险箱。
This isn't the secret formula.
这不是秘密公式。
It's a to-do list.
这是一个待办事项清单。
Huh?
啊？
What happened to
the Krusty Krab?
发生了什么事
蟹堡王？
What happened to
the Chum Bucket?
发生了什么事
密友桶？
Plankton: Curses.
浮游生物：诅咒。
This isn't what I meant
by renovation.
这不是我的意思
通过翻新。
I know, isn't it great?
我知道，这不是很好吗？
It looks just like
the Krusty Krab.
它看起来就像
蟹堡王。
Mr. Krabs: It looks more like
Plankton trying to steal
me restaurant.
蟹老板：看起来更像是
浮游生物试图偷窃
我的餐厅。
Mr. Krabs, you've returned
from your vacation.
蟹老板你回来了
从你的假期开始。
And it's time for
the Krusty Krab to return
from  its  vacation.
现在是时候了
蟹堡王回归
从它的假期开始。
Hooray.
万岁。
And I bet you tried
to steal this too.
我打赌你尝试过
也来偷这个。
Well, "steal" is such
a strong word.
嗯，“偷”就是这样
一个强烈的词。
You don't really think I'd leave
me secret formula behind
when I go on vacation, do you?
你真的认为我不会离开
我背后的秘密公式
当我去度假时，你呢？
Now, stay away from me...
现在，离我远点……
...restaurant, bug.
...餐厅，虫子。
I think we've been
through this before.
我想我们已经
之前通过这个。
Allow me to do the honors.
请允许我履行这一荣誉。
Ahh...
啊...
Oh, excellent job, genius.
哦，干得好，天才。
You really fixed the place up.
你真的把这个地方修好了。
Don't nag me, Karen.
别跟我唠叨，凯伦。
I've had a long day.
我度过了漫长的一天。
Yep, Squidward,
you really outdid yourself
with the new decor.
是的，章鱼哥，
你真的超越了自己
与新的装饰。
Where'd you get the fountain?
你从哪里得到的喷泉？
That, I sculpted out of
the concrete foundation
of the Chum Bucket.
那是我雕刻出来的
混凝土基础
密友桶的。
And all these metal decorations?
还有所有这些金属装饰品？
Those were all fabricated
from the Chum Bucket walls.
那些都是编造的
从 Chum Bucket 的墙上。
And the computer?
电脑呢？
Oh, that's Plankton's wife.
哦，那是浮游生物的妻子。
Well, it looks great, lad,
and it didn't cost me a dime.
嗯，看起来很棒，小伙子
而且我没花一毛钱。
Wow, $25 for a Krabby Patty?
哇，25 美元一份蟹肉饼？
Ripoff, dude.
盗版，伙计。
Not cool.
不酷。
But you're paying for
the enhanced ambience, dude.
但你正在付出代价
增强的氛围，伙计。
Well, that's true.
嗯，确实如此。
It is pretty classy in here.
这里非常优雅。
Give me four.
给我四个。